

# VŨ ĐỨC ĐỘ AI ENGINEER

#### **ABOUT ME**

I have over 3 years of experience working at product companies as an Al Engineer. My main responsibility is building systems and solving problems by using Machine Learning and Al technology. In addition, I have tasks and skills data collection, processing, management, and analysis.

# CONTACT







💡 Cầu Giấy - Hà Nội

# **EDUCATION**

Military Technical Academy (MTA) 2015 - 2020

- Major in Data Technology
- Degree: Very Good (3.39/4)

# **SKILLS**

- Data processing, Data Mining, Web Scraping
- NLP, Computer vision, Speech
- · Technology:
  - o Redash, Metabase
  - MongoDB, MySQL, PostgresSQL, Clickhouse, Redis
  - Docker, RabbitMQ, Kafka, MinIO, S3

#### **EXPERIENCES**



**TEPA 2021 - now** 

- Researching and developing Speech to Text Vietnamese project.
- Researching and developing Text to Speech Vietnamese project
- Building Vietnamese CRM Chatbot.
- Building VoiceBot for Cenhomes Sales Department.
- Building Virtual assistant system for reporting business situation.
- Analyzing and upgrading system: CRM, ERP.



2019 - 2021

- Researching and developing Real Estate Price Prediction System by machine learning.
- · Researching and developing **Recommendation System.**
- Researching Text to speech project.
- **♦ VNPT IT 2017 2019** Intern Pentester
  - · Testing and defining website vulnerability.
  - Using Linux, deploy environment for case studies.
  - Using **Python** for resolving issues such as crawling information, processing data, automatic modules, ...

# **ACHIEVEMENT**

- Top 1 graduation project 2020
- 1st in MTA Softcon Contest 07/2020.
- 3rd in HCM City Al Challenge, Scene Text Recognition - 12/2021.
- Paper: Vu Duc Do and Tran Cao Truong, "Applying Machine Learning to Estimate Residential House Prices in Hanoi", The 23rd National Conference on Information Technology and Communication, 2020.

### **DETAIL OF PROJECTS**

# +

**TEPA 2021 - now** 

- Speech-to-Text Vietnamese
  - o Team size: 3
  - o Position: member
  - Technology Used: Python, Deep Learning(sequence-to-sequence)
- Text to Speech Vietnamese:
  - Team size: 3
  - o Position: member
  - Technology Used: Python, FlaskAPI, Deep learning(FastPitch, G2P)
- Vietnamese CRM Chatbot.
  - o Team size: 2
  - o Position: member
  - o Technology Used: Python, RaSa
- VoiceBot for Cenhomes Sales Department
  - o Team size: 3
  - o Position: member
  - Technology Used: Python, RaSa,
    Speech2Text, Text2Speech
- Virtual assistant system
  - o Team size: 3
  - o Position: member
  - Technology Used: Python, RaSa,
    Speech2Text, Text2Speech

#### **+**

2019 - 2021

- Real Estate Price Prediction System
  - o Team size: 6
  - o Position: main developer
  - Technology Used: Python, FlaskAPI, Machine learning(linear regression,KNN, Decision Tree, Random Forest,...), S3, MongoDB
- Recommendation System.
  - o Team size: 4
  - o Position: main developer
  - Technology Used: Python, FlaskAPI, Machine learning, Kafka, Clickhouse, CronJob
- Text to Speech Vietnamese:
  - o Team size: 3
  - o Position: main developer
  - Technology Used: Python, FlaskAPI,Deep learning(Tacotron2, FastSpeech, G2P)

#### +

#### Other

- Scene Text Recognition
  - o Team size: 2
  - Position: member
  - o Technology Used: Python, Yolo v5, OCR